He's got an opinion
on everything, Ima.
He's like a walking calculator.
He even calculated
how much I spent helping
with those dentures.
Isn't it better that you
really get to know him
before you get married?
But let me remind you, dear.
You don't have to force it.
We'll get through this.
I can't just
give up on him, Ima.
What the hell?!
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Well, that's good.
You two talk for a while.
Alright. Bye!
[HUFFS]
Why didn't you say anything?
Do I have to talk
while I'm eating?
Why didn't you look
where you're sitting?
[KEYPAD CLICKING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[PING] Have you eaten yet?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[KEYPAD CLICKING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYPAD CLICKING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[JUNE] Leftover rice
is your favorite, right?
Why'd you give it to me?
[KEYPAD CLICKING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEYPAD CLICKING]
[SHERYN] I thought
they hated each other.
They seem to be getting close.
[PHONE CHIMES]
"Let's ruin Ping in June's eyes
so she'll call off
the wedding herself."
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]